"迷失" 前情提要...
Previously on "Lost"...
噢 天啊
Oh, god.
她的死是我的错 不是你的
It's not your fault she's dead. It's mine.
我说服她留下 因为我不想孤单的一个人
I convinced her to stay because I didn't want to be alone.
你在晚上之前就能到达寺庙
You can probably make it back to the temple by nightfall.
很抱歉让你看到我这个样子
I'm sorry you had to see me like that.
你好 Richard
Hello, Richard.
- 你?  - 就是我
- You?  - Me.
我对你们很失望!
I am very disappointed in all of you!
你去澳洲干嘛?
So what were you doing in Australia?
- 出差还是观光?  - 其实我是去徒步旅行
- Business or pleasure?  - Actually, I went on a walkabout.
欢迎来到洛杉矶
Welcome to Los Angeles.
- 拜 爸爸  - 拜 亲爱的
- Bye, daddy.  - Bye, sweetie.
哦 拜托
Oh, come on.
John啊?
John?
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
嗯 我还行
Yeah. I'm fine.
噢
Oh.
来 让... 让我扶你进去
Come on, let's... let's get you inside.
好
Okay.
那要多长时间?
Well, how long will that take?
婚礼在十月举行
The wedding is in October.
呃 我回头再给你打 好
Look, I'm gonna just have to call you back. Yeah.
我烦死这些酒会承办人
I am so sick of caterers
和乐队了
and bands
还有选椅子背的花色
and picking fabrics for chair backs.
你觉得就请...
What do you say we just...
我父母和你父亲 在拉斯维加斯
get my parents and your dad
举办一个简单的婚礼 怎么样?
and do it shotgun style in Vegas?
不 Helen 你应该得到更好的
No. You deserve better than that, Helen.
我们能做到 我知道我们能
And we can do this. I know we can.
我喜欢...
I like...
这个
this one.
- 那个?  - 我是说这个
- That one?  - I meant this one.
你真贴心
You are a very sweet man.
我知道
I know.
会议怎么样?
So how was the conference?
无聊
Boring.
谁是Jack Shephard医生?
Who's, uh, who's Dr. Jack Shephard?
噢 填报失表的时候
Oh, I met him at lost luggage,
在丢失行李处遇到的
when I went to fill out the forms.
他... 他也丢了个东西
He... he lost something, too.
他是脊椎医生?
He's a spinal surgeon?
嗯 人很好
Yeah. Nice guy.
他给了我一次免费询诊
He offered me a free consult.
你应该给他打电话
You should call him.
哦 Helen 他只是出于礼貌
Oh, he was just being polite, Helen.
那又怎样?
So what?
我是说...
I mean...
你碰上一个脊椎医生 这多巧啊?
What are the odds of you just running into a spinal surgeon?
我是说 谁能解释?
I mean, who knows?
也许这就是命运
Maybe it's destiny.
没准儿是吧
Maybe it is.
好吧 Richard
All right, Richard.
是时候谈谈了
Time to talk.
欢迎回来 上校
Welcome back, Colonel.
哇
Wow.
你在澳洲晒得不错
You got a nice tan in Australia.
想我们吗?
Did you miss us?
当然想 Randy
Sure I did, Randy.
那么... John 会开得怎么样?
So... how was the conference, John?
噢 还行 我没学到什么东西
Uh, it was okay. I didn't really learn anything.
- 没有?  - 但是 呃 我认识了几个人
- No?  - But, um, I made some good contacts, though.
真的? 很有趣
Really? That's interesting.
是这样 Ken Fisher打电话说 你取消了跟他的午餐
See, uh, Ken Fisher called and said you had to cancel your lunch with him.
是的 是的 我那天不太舒服
Right, right. I was a little under the weather that day.
- 哦... 可能是时差  - 真的吗?
- Uh...  probably jet lag.  - Really?
因为后来会议人员给我打电话
Cause then the seminar people called
说你没有拿你的入场券
and said you hadn't picked up your credentials.
我查了一下
I did some checking,
你好像什么活动都没参加
and it seems that you didn't attend a single event.
我们是公费把你送去悉尼的...
Since we sent you to Sydney on the company's dime...
你到底去哪了?
where the hell were you?
Randy 我很抱歉 我...
Look, Randy, I'm really sorry. I'm...
为什么不把这当作假期呢?
Why don't we just call it my vacation week?
我认为你想在10月份放假
I thought you wanted that vacation week in October?
你知道的 为了你的婚礼
You know, for your wedding.
求你了 Randy 我... 我知道不应该说谎
Please, Randy. I... I know I shouldn't have lied.
但是我去哪了...
But where I was...
是个人隐私
It's personal,
而且我... 我真的不想说这件事
and I... and I really don't want to talk about it.
好吧 John
Okay, John.
嘿 你被解雇了
Hey, you're fired.
渴吗?
Thirsty?
Richard 很抱歉我打了你的嗓喉咙
Richard, I'm sorry I hit you in the throat
还把你拉出沙滩 但我必须要做些什么
and dragged you off the beach, but I had to do something.
- 你想干嘛?  - 我一直想...
- What do you want?  - What I've always wanted...
让你跟我走
for you to come with me.
为什么你这么像John Locke?
Why do you look like John Locke?
我知道他会带我找到Jacob
I knew he'd get me access to Jacob,
因为John是接班人
because John's a candidate,
至少曾经是
or at least he was a candidate.
你的意思是...
What do you mean...
你说什么"接班人"?
What do you mean, "a candidate"?
- Jacob没有告诉你这件事吗?  - 告诉我什么?
- Didn't Jacob tell you any of this?  - Any of what?
哦 Richard 我很抱歉
Oh, Richard, I'm sorry.
你是指 你一直按照他的吩咐去做
You mean, you've been doing everything he told you
而他却始终没有告诉你为什么?
all this time, and he never said why?
我绝不会那样对你
I would never have done that to you.
我也绝不会对你有所隐瞒
I would never have kept you in the dark.
那... 你会怎么做?
And... and what would you have done?
我会对你以礼相待
I would have treated you with respect.
跟我来
Come with me,
我保证会告诉你一切
and I promise I'll tell you everything.
不
No.
Richard 你确定吗?
Are you sure about that, Richard?
机不可失 失不再来
Because people seldom get a second chance.
我不会跟你去任何地方
I'm not going anywhere with you.
那好吧...
All right...
怎么了?
What?
待会见 Richard 我去去就来
I'll be seeing you, Richard, sooner than you think.
打扰你了吗?
Am I interrupting?
告诉我 他们发生了什么事
Tell me what happened to them.
好吧
All right.
你有很合理的理由 质疑我所说的话
There's a fairly reasonable chance that you won't believe me.
说来听听
Try me.
是John Locke杀了他们
John Locke killed them.
- 全是他一人所为吗?  - 是的
- All by himself?  - Yes.
他化作一股黑烟
He turned into a pillar of black smoke,
就在我眼前 把他们全杀了
and he killed them right before my eyes.
Jacob也被杀了吗?
Did it kill Jacob as well?
是的
Yes.
那他的尸体在哪儿?
Then where's his body?
Locke将他踢入火堆 现在早已化成了灰烬
Locke kicked him into the fire, and he burned away.
Locke... 你知道他为什么 将Richard带进丛林吗?
Locke... do you know why he carried Richard out into the jungle?
他是在招募新人
He's recruiting.
你好啊 James
Hello, James.
我以为你死了呢
I thought you were dead.
是啊
I am,
我就在这儿等死呢
here's to bein' dead.
这样非常好啊
You're taking this extremely well.
什么非常好?
Taking what extremely well?
我还活着站在这里啊
That I'm here.
我才不在乎你是死是活
I don't give a damn if you're dead
你是时空旅行...
or time travelin' or...
或是被圣诞节幽灵带走 于我何干
the ghost of christmas past.
我只在意这杯威士忌
All I care about is this whiskey.
来 干完这杯
So bottom's up,
然后滚出我的屋子
then get the hell out of my house.
这间屋子不是你的 James
This isn't your house, James.
不是我的又怎样
The hell it ain't.
不 你仅仅是在这儿住过一段时间
No. You just lived here for a while.
这屋子永远不会是你的
This was never your house.
你是谁?
Who are you?
你一定不是John Locke
You sure as hell ain't John Locke.
为什么这么说?
What makes you say that?
因为Locke很胆小
Cause Locke was scared,
就算他佯装镇定 也一样
even when he was pretending he wasn't.
但是你...
But you...
你并不胆小
You ain't scared.
如果我告诉你 我是唯一通晓玄机的人
What if I told you I was the person who could answer
又该怎么说呢?
the most important question in the world?
什么玄机?
And what question is that?
你为什么会在这所岛上?
Why are you on this island?
我会在这所岛上
I'm on this island
是因为我乘坐的飞机坠毁了
because my plane crashed,
飞机在空中炸毁
'cause my flight blew up,
还有 我驾驶的直升机载荷过重
because the helicopter I was on was ridin' one too heavy.
那不是你在这里的原因
That's not why you're here.
如果你愿意跟我来...
And if you come with me...
我就能向你证实
I can prove it.
好吧 我得先穿好裤子
Well, I guess I better put some pants on.
好的
Okay.
靠!
Come on!
噢 去死吧!
Aw, damn it!
老兄?
Dude?
老兄!
Dude!
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
我要干什么? 你他妈的要干什么?
What am I doing? What the hell are you doing?
你这辈子停过车吗?
You ever park a car in your life?
你几乎占了我的车位!
You're practically in my spot!
- 我很抱歉  - 哼
- I'm sorry.  - Yeah.
但是 看 那边有一个残疾人专用停车位
But, you know, there's a handicap spot right over here.
是 是有 但有谁规定我必须停在那了
Yeah. Yeah, okay. But I don't have to park there.
我可以想停哪儿就停哪儿
I can park anywhere I want.
而你 只需要把车停在自己的车位里
You need to stay inside the lines.
真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
他们本该给我预留一个车位的
They were supposed to reserve a spot for me.
可是 哎  所以我只能停这儿了
So, you know, I just parked here.
我从来没见过你 你在这个公司工作吗?
I haven't seen you before. You work here?
事实上 这是我的公司
Actually, I own the company.
我是Hugo Reyes
Hugo Reyes.
我是John Locke
John Locke.
好 你是做什么工作的 John?
Cool. What do you do here, John?
呃 实际上 什么都不是 我的上司刚把我炒了
Uh, actually, nothing. My boss just fired me.
哦? 谁是你的上司?
Oh? Who's your boss?
他叫Randy
His name is Randy.
- 不过 呃...  - 是Randy Nations?
- But, uh...  - Randy Nations?
对 就是他
Yeah. Yes.
哦 那可是个十足的蠢货
Yeah, that guy is a huge douche.
想让我帮你向他求情吗?
You want me to talk to him for ya?
不 没关系的
No, that's okay.
听着 John
Tell you what, John.
我还有一个临时代理处
I own a temp agency, too.
打这个电话
Call this number
告诉他们 Hugo说了
and tell them that Hugo said
要给你安排一份新工作 马上
to hook you up with a new job pronto.
打起精神来
And chin up.
一切都会好起来的
Things are gonna work out.
他已经开始腐烂了
He's getting pretty ripe.
人都去哪儿了?
Where is everybody?
走了 他们说要到寺庙那去
They left. They said they were going to the temple.
目前 那是岛上最安全的地方
Right now it's the safest place on the island.
- 我们也该去那儿  - 你还好吗?
- We should go there, too.  - Are you all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
来吧 咱们离开这儿
Come on, let's get out of here.
你凭什么认为 我会跟你走?
What makes you think that I'm going with you?
因为你想要找到Jin
Because you want to find Jin.
你知道他现在的情况?
What do you know about my husband?
我知道如果他还活着 还在这个岛上
I know that if he's on the island and he's alive,
那他一定是在寺庙里
then he'll be at the temple.
我们走吧
Let's get moving.
John怎么办?
What about John?
我们得把他埋了
We need to bury him.
你一个人在那个房子里都干什么 James?
What were you doing alone in that house, James?
喝酒
Drinking.
- 你其他朋友都哪儿去了?  - 一些去了寺庙 一些 其它地方
- Where are the rest of your friends?  - Some, temple, somewhere.
你为什么不跟他们一起去呢?
Why aren't you with them?
你猜怎么着? 咱们就安安静静的走 成吗?
You know what? How about we just don't talk?
听你的
You got it.
他是谁?
Who the hell is that?
你能看见他?
You can see him?
那孩子? 靠 对 我当然看得见他
The kid? Hell, yeah, I can see him.
嘿!
Hey!
你知道规矩
You know the rules.
你不能杀他
You can't kill him.
不要告诉我 什么不能做
Don't tell me what I can't do.
不要告诉我 什么不能做!
Don't tell me what I can't do!
Locke! Locke呀!
Locke! Locke!
听着 不管你是谁 给你20秒钟 给我出来
Look, whoever you are, you got about 20  seconds,
否则 我就走了!
and then I'm outta here!
- 他呢?  - 你在这儿干什么?
- Where is he?  - What the hell are you doing here?
- 他在哪儿?  - Locke? 追着一个小孩进丛林里了
- Where is he?  - Locke? Ran off into the jungle after some kid.
- 我们得马上走 现在  - 去哪?
- We need to go, now.  - Go where?
- 去寺庙 快走 快走  - 你知道吗?
- To the temple. Let's go. Let's go.  - You know what?
我去过寺庙了 而现在 我要跟着Locke
I've been to the temple. I think I'm sticking with Locke.
- 他不是John Locke  - 我知道
- That man is not John Locke.  - I know.
- 那你为什么还要和他在一起?  - 因为他知道答案
- Then why are you with him?  - Because he's got answers,
他说他知道我来到这个岛上的真正原因...
says he knows why I'm on this island...
- 除非你愿意告诉我 Richard  - 别天真了
- unless you wanna tell me why I'm here, Richard.  - Don't be naive.
- 他什么都不会告诉你的 他要杀了你  - 如果他要杀我
- He's not gonna tell you anything. He's gonna kill you.  - If he wanted to kill me,
- 他都可以 杀死我十几次了  - 你不明白
- he could've done it a dozen times already.  - You don't understand what you're dealing with.
他不只想要你死 他要置每个人于死地...
He doesn't just want you dead. He wants everyone dead...
你关心的每个人... 所有人... 他不会善罢甘休的...
everyone you care about... all of them... and he won't stop...
你在和谁说话?
Who you talking to?
没人啊
Nobody.
你追上那个孩子了吗?
You ever catch up with the kid?
什么孩子?
What kid?
好
Right.
咱们上路吧 好吗?
Let's get on with it, shall we?
好 James 咱们赶紧上路
Yes, James. Les get on with it.
你会把自己描述为哪种动物?
What kind of animal would you describe yourself as?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
你会把自己描述为哪种动物?
What kind of animal would you describe yourself as?
呃... 我... 我不知道这跟我的工作有什么关系...
Uh... I... I don't know what that has to do with...
想到什么就说什么
Just say whatever comes to mind.
你是不是想把自己 描述成人类个人?
Would you describe yourself as a people person?
我能不能找你的上司谈谈?
May I speak to your supervisor?
当然可以
Of course.
我去找她
I'll go get her.
早上好 Locke先生?
Good morning, Mr. Locke?
是
Yeah.
我是Rose Nadler 办公室主任
I'm Rose Nadler, the office supervisor.
有什么需要帮忙的?
What can I do for you?
呃 Nadler女士 您能帮我的是
Uh, what you can do, Ms. Nadler,
别让我回答 我是什么动物 这种问题
is to spare me the question about what kind of animal I am
并且希望您给我一份工作
and hopefully place me in a job.
没问题
Absolutely.
你想做什么样的工作?
What kind of placement are you looking for?
我看到你们这儿
Well, I see here
需要一个工地协调员
that you have a listing for a site coordinator.
建筑工地协调员
Construction site coordinator.
呃 我不太确定这职位适合您
Uh, I'm not sure that's a good match.
- 如果您关心的是工作经验的话 我有很多...  - 工作经验不是问题
- Well, if experience is the issue, I have...  - Experience isn't the issue.
瞧 Reyes先生告诉我
Look, Mr. Reyes told me
如果我过来 你们就会给我安排好
if I came down here, I would be taken care of.
Reyes先生是我的老板 如果他那样说
And Mr. Reyes is my boss, so if he said that,
我就会这样做
I can make it happen for you.
如果你想做建筑 你就做吧
If you want to work construction, you got it.
- 谢谢  - 我还没说完
- Thank you.  - I'm not finished.
明天我会让你到工地去
I will send you down there tomorrow,
后天
and then the day after,
你再来我的办公室
you will be back in my office.
听着...
Look...
Locke先生 我们还是比较现实一点吧
Mr. Locke, let's try to be a little more realistic.
你又对现实有多了解?
And what do you know about realistic?
我患了癌症
I have cancer.
晚期
Terminal cancer.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
当大夫第一次告诉我时
When the doctors first told me,
我很难接受
I had a hard time accepting it.
但最终 我接受了事实
But eventually, I got past the denial part
并且我准备好好珍惜 剩下的一分一秒
and I got back to living whatever life I've got left.
所以...
So...
要不我们帮你找一份
How about we find you a job
你适合的工作?
you can do?
你看书么?
Do you read?
你说啥?
Excuse me?
你看不看书?
Books. You read books?
当然 谁不看书?
Sure. Who doesn't?
我最喜欢的是斯坦贝克的 "人与鼠"
My favorite's Steinbeck, "Of Mice and Men."
你听说过么?
You know that one?
没 跟我不是一个年代
Nope. A little after my time.
讲的是两个人George和Lennie
It's about these two guys, George and Lennie.
Lennie反应有点慢
Lennie's kind of slow,
会给George惹麻烦
causing George problems.
所以George带他走进森林
So George walks him out in the woods,
叫他朝那边看 并且描绘说
tells him to look out yonder and picture
他们将来要在那儿 住漂亮的小房子
the pretty little house they're gonna live in one day.
之后他朝Lennie脑袋后面开了一枪
and he shoots Lennie in the back of the head.
好吧 听起来不是个大团圆结局
Well, that doesn't sound like a happy ending.
的确
It isn't.
- 你在想什么呢 James?  - 我在寻思如果我朝你
- What's on your mind, James?  - I'm wondering what would happen to you
脑袋后面开一枪 你会怎么样
if I put a bullet in your head.
嗯 要不我们试试?
Mm. Why don't we find out?
你到底是什么东西?
What are you?
我是个被困住的人
What I am is trapped.
被困住了很长一段时间
and I've been trapped for so long
以至于 我都忘了自由的感觉
that I don't even remember what it feels like to be free.
也许你能理解
Maybe you can understand that.
我被困之前 我是一个普通人 像你一样 James
But before I was trapped, I was a man, James, just like you.
我才不信
I have a hard time believing that.
好吧 随你信不信 但那是事实
Well, you can believe whatever you want, but that's the truth.
我知道什么是 快乐
I know what it's like to feel joy,
痛苦 愤怒 恐惧...
to feel pain, anger, fear...
什么是被背叛的滋味
to experience betrayal.
我也知道 失去深爱之人的感觉
I know what it's like to lose someone you love.
如果你要开枪 就动手吧
If you wanna shoot me, shoot me.
但是你已经离得很近了 James
But you're so close, James.
现在回头 太可惜了
It would be such a shame to turn back now.
为什么一开始 你们要把他带到雕像那儿去?
Why did you have to bring him to the statue in the first place?
因为那儿的人们
Because the people there
需要知道他们的敌人长什么样
need to see the face of what they're up against.
那又怎么样能阻止他们的敌人
And what's to stop what they're up against
变模样呢?
from changing his face?
他现在变不了了
He can't. Not anymore.
这条路他走不通了
He's stuck this way.
有没有人想说些什么?
Does anyone want to say anything?
都没人认识他吗?
Didn't any of you know him?
好吧 我认识他
All right, I knew him.
John Locke是一位...
John Locke was a...
信徒 他有自己的信仰
a believer. He was a man of faith.
他...
He was...
我永远成为不了...
a much better man...
他那样的人...
than I will ever be...
我非常抱歉 杀害了他
And I'm very sorry I murdered him.
这鬼葬礼是我参加过的
This is the weirdest damn funeral
最诡异的了
I've ever been to.
你好 Shephard医生办公室
Hello. Dr. Shephard's office.
喂?
Hello?
需要找谁?
Can I help you?
不 我谁都不找
No. No, you can't.
你在跟谁打电话?
Who was that on the phone?
呃 没人
Mm, no one.
没人?
No one?
John 我刚才确实听到你在讲电话
John, I just heard you talking on the phone.
我 呃
I was, uh,
我刚才是打给Shephard医生的
I was calling Dr. Shephard.
好啊 不错啊 你准备什么时候去见他?
Well, good for you. when are you gonna see him?
我不打算见他
I'm not gonna see him.
- 呃 我... 不懂 你为什么不打算...  - 我被解雇了 Helen
- Well, I... I don't understand. Why wouldn't you want...  - I got fired, Helen.
来了!
Coming!
女士? 我是大洋航空快件员
Ma'am? Oceanic courier.
这是之前我们弄丢的行李
I'm delivering your lost luggage.
好的
All right.
麻烦您在这签个字
Sign here to accept the delivery.
- 谢谢  - 好的 谢谢
- Thanks.  - Okay, thanks.
好吧 John
Okay, John.
现在跟我谈谈吧
Now talk to me.
你为什么被解雇了?
How did you get fired?
我跟Randy撒谎了 我没去参加悉尼的会议
I lied to Randy. I didn't go to the conference in Sydney.
什么?
What?
Helen 把箱子打开
Open the case, Helen.
这... 这些是干嘛的?
W... What are these for?
我的徒步旅行
My walkabout.
你... 你... 的什么?
Your... y... your what?
徒步旅行
My walkabout.
内地的一次冒险
An adventure in the outback
在野外生存
Man against nature.
但他们不让我去
But they wouldn't let me go.
所以... 我坐着向他们喊
And... and I sat there yelling at them,
对着他们吼
shouting at them,
别跟我说 什么事情我做不了
that they couldn't tell me what I can't do.
可他们说得对
But they were right.
我受够了想象
I'm sick of imagining
能站起来之后的生活 Helen
what my life could be out of this chair, Helen,
受够了想象...
what it would be like to...
能站起来和你结婚
walk down the aisle with you,
因为这根本不可能发生
'cause it's not gonna happen.
但如果你想让我多看几个医生
So if you need me to see more doctors,
呃... 多咨询几次
if, uh... have more consults,
如果你想要我站起来
if you need me to get out of this chair,
我不会怪你
I don't blame you.
可我不希望你用尽一生
But I don't want you to spend your life
来等待这个奇迹 Helen 因为...
waiting for a miracle, Helen, because...
根本就没有奇迹
there is no such thing.
奇迹是有的 John
There are miracles, John.
可我唯一...
And the only thing...
在等待的...
I was ever waitin' for...
就是你
was you.
景色不错
Nice view.
接下来呢?
Now what?
现在我们下去
Now we go down.
下去哪儿?
Down where?
下去那儿
Down there.
无意冒犯 你是已经死了
No offense, but you already died,
你当然不觉得有什么大不了
so it's great that this is not a big deal for you.
可你要是认为 我会先下去
But if you think I'm climbin' down there first,
你就真他妈疯了
you are off your damn nut.
没关系 我先下去
It's no problem. I'll go first.
你下来吗 James?
You comin', James?
James啊!
James!
Locke啊!
Locke!
跳呀 抓住我 快点!
Jump. I got you. come on!
快点 抓住我! 快点!
Come on, I got you! come on!
快点!
Come on!
呃! 快点!
Uhh! Come on!
啊! 小心!
Aah! Look out!
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
这究竟是怎么回事?
What the hell's that all about?
天大的笑话
Inside joke.
这就是你想让我看的...
So this is what you wanted me to see...
悬崖壁洞里 天平上摆着的几块石头?
a hole in the cliff with some rocks on the cale?
这就是我会在岛上的原因?
That's why I'm here?
不是
No.
那才是你会在岛上的原因
That's why you're here.
James 那就是你们会在岛上的原因
That, James, is why you're all here.
好的 做到位 加油 保持这样
All right, dig it out. Come on. All the way.
不要作弊 快点 加油 保持这样
No cheatin'. Come on, now. Come on, all the way.
你们可以赶上 你们可以赶上
You can catch 'em. You can catch 'em.
加油 做到位
Come on, dig it out.
现在冲刺 保持冲刺状态
Bring it in now. Bring it in all the way.
好样的 好样的
Good job. Good job.
好了 同学们!
All right, everyone!
请把课本翻到第四章
Please open your textbooks to chapter four.
今天我们要讲...
Today we are going to talk about...
人类的生殖系统
the human reproductive system.
你知道教...
Do you know where the teach...
不好意思 能告诉我教师休息室在哪儿吗?
Excuse me. Can you tell me where the teachers' lounge is?
- 嗯 就在那儿  - 谢谢
- Yeah, it's over there.  - thank you.
好了 大家 我知道我像个跳线的唱片喋喋不休
All right, people, I know I sound like a broken record,
可我还要再说多少次才行?
but how many times do we have to go over this?
如果谁喝完最后一杯咖啡
If you have the last cup of coffee,
请把滤纸拿下来
you remove the filter
丢掉
and throw it away.
别担心 我会煮一壶新的
Fear not. I will make a fresh pot.
其实我只想喝点伯爵红茶
Actually, I was just hoping for some earl grey.
茶?
Tea?
现在总算有人要绅士饮品了
Now there's a gentleman's drink.
我们好像还没见过 我叫Ben Linus 教欧洲历史
I don't believe we've met. Ben Linus. European history.
- 我叫John Locke 是代课教师  - 嗯 欢迎你
- John Locke. Substitute.  - Well, welcome.
这些都是谁写的?
Who wrote all this?
一个曾叫"Jacob"的人
His name was Jacob.
曾叫"Jacob"?
"Was" Jacob?
他昨天死了
He died yesterday.
你看起来倒不是太难过
You don't seem too upset about it.
我不难过
I'm not.
为什么这些名字都被划掉了?
Why are all the names crossed out?
没有都划掉
They're not all crossed out.
"Shephard"没划掉
"Shephard."
是指Jack Shephard?
That'd be Jack Shephard?
不只他
And he's not the only one.
"Reyes."也没
"Reyes."
就是Hugo 对吧?
that's Hugo, right?
- 这个8是什么意思?  - Jacob对数字很痴迷
- What's the 8 about?  - Jacob had a thing for numbers.
有"16 Jarrah"
"16. Jarrah."
有"42 Kwon"
"42. Kwon."
我不知道指的是Sun还是Jin
I don't know if it's Sun or if it's Jin.
这儿
Here.
还有"4 Locke"
"4. Locke."
我想我们俩都认识他
I think both know him.
最后同样重要的...
Last but not least...
"15号 Ford"
"number 15. Ford."
就是你
That would be you.
他把我名字写在这面墙上干嘛?
Why would he write my name on this wall?
- 我又没见过他  - 哦 不 你肯定见过他
- I never even met the guy.  - Oh, no, I'm sure you did meet Jacob.
就在你生命的某个重要时刻 James
At some point in your life, James,
很可能在你还很小
probably when you were young,
很可怜 很脆弱的时候 他找过你
when you were miserable and vulnerable, he came to you.
他操纵着你
He manipulated you,
把你当成木偶那样操纵
pulled your strings like you were a puppet.
结果 你以为是你自己做的那些选择
And as a result, choices that you thought you made
事实上根本就不是选择
were never really choices at all.
他在逼迫你 James
He was pushing you, James.
逼迫你...
Pushing you...
来到这个岛上
to the island.
那他究竟为什么要这么做?
Why the hell would he do that?
因为你是接班人之一
Because you're a candidate.
什么的接班人?
Candidate for what?
他认为自己是这个地方的守护者
He thought he was the protector of this place.
而你 James 已经被提名...
And you, James, have been nominated...
来接手那份使命
to take over that job.
那意味着什么?
What does that mean?
意味着你有三个选择
It means you've got three choices.
第一个选择 你可以什么都不做...
First, you can do nothing and...
静观其变
see how all this plays out.
这样很可能
And possibly,
你的名字...
your name...
就会被划掉
will get crossed out.
第二个选择就是
Second option,
你可以接下这份使命
you can accept the job,
成为新的Jacob 来守护这个岛
become the new Jacob and protect the island.
守护它什么?
Protect it from what?
没有什么 James
From nothing, James.
这就是那个天大的笑话
That's the joke.
根本没什么好守护的
There's nothing to protect it from.
就是个破岛而已
It's just a damn island.
没有Jacob或你 或其他任何被他荒废生命的人
And it will be perfectly fine without Jacob or you
这岛都会好好的 继续存在
or any of the other people whose lives he wasted.
你说了有三个选择
You said there were three choices.
第三个 James 就是我们离开
The third choice, James, is that we just go.
只要我们离开这个岛
We just get the hell off this island
永远地忘掉它
and we never look back.
那怎么才能做到?
And how do we do that?
我们一起
Together.
你说呢 James?
So what do you say, James?
准备好回家了吗?
Are you ready to go home?
管他呢 好的
Hell, yes.